



A UX/interaction designer by training, now a software engineer by trade, specialising in front end technologies. I love working with others to create design systems that scale and accessible interfaces that delight - not just for the users that interact with them, but also for the designers that leverage them and the developers that deploy them.

Experience

Software Engineer (Front End Lead), SparesCNX; Singapore - Sep 2019 - Present

- Primary ownership of the flagship field tablet application, navigating uniquely challenging use cases and limitations with a team of engineers, e.g. hardware integration with on-tablet RFID scanner, low-connectivity environment, on-device database synchronisation etc.
- Key maintainer of React Native codebase, ensuring high standards of performance, architecture, readability, style consistency, testing coverage, documentation and release/deployment practices.

Software Development Consultant, Maltem Consulting Group; Singapore – May 2017 - Aug 2019

- Developed e-commerce applications, internal tools, libraries and design systems across the full stack of web technologies as a software engineer at AXA.
- Developed behaviour-driven development (BDD) automated testing frameworks and strategies for web applications as a QA engineer at SGX.
- Planned and participated in design sprints for both internal and other client projects as a UX Designer.
- Developed technical assessment strategies and interviewed potential candidates for new consultants.

UX Design Intern, Sonoport; Singapore - May 2016 - Jun 2016

- Worked with product design team to test application iterations through interviews and user testing.
- Processed test data to create actionable design insights that translated into real design decisions.
- Created style guidelines, UX flows and interactive prototypes to facilitate the design and development process.

Education/Certifications

National University of Singapore

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) with Honours, Communications and New Media - Class of 2016

General Assembly; Singapore

Web Development Immersive - November 2016 - March 2017

Professional Scrum Master I

Scrum.org - August 2017

Skills

- Design/media assets: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma, Sketch, Keynote, Ableton Live
- Front: React, React Native, Next.js, Sass, Redux, Web components, Gatsby, Hugo, three.js
- Back: **Node.js, Typescript**, Ruby
- Tooling: **ESLint, Prettier, Parcel**, Webpack, Storybook
- Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, PouchDB, CouchDB
- Testing: Cypress, Jest, React Testing Library, Webdriver, Enzyme, Mocha